jensholvoet.com 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy |

This privacy policy sets out how JensHolvoet.com uses and protects any information that you give me (Jens Holvoet) when you use this website. I’m committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should I ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### **What I collect**

I may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### **What I do with the information**

I require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * I may use the information to improve the quality of the information on the website
  * I may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which I think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided

### **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Website owners use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps them analyze data about webpage traffic and improve the website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

Websites only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help the website owners to provide you with a better website, by enabling them to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### **Links to other websites**

Any website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave this website, you should note that I don’t have any control over that other website. Therefore, I can’t be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### **Regarding your personal information**

I don’t sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless I have your permission to do so. I may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which I think you may find interesting.

If you believe that any information I’m holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email me as soon as possible. I will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
